Hassan Mostafa

iOS Developer

Mobile software architect and developer specializing in Swift and reactive programming on the iOS platform. Passionate about creating great user experiences, designing beautiful user interfaces, and writing elegant code. Constantly striving to improve skills and learn new technologies.

hassanmostafa545@gmail.com 🔀

00201000635811

5th settlement, New Cairo, Egypt 👂

linkedin.com/in/hassan-mostafa-950b62159 in

github.com/Hassan-iOS

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior iOS developer

Minds Outsourcing

01/2019 - Present

iOS Developer / Freelancer

TUNGA

09/2018 - Present

Amsterdam, Netherlands

iOS Developer

i-vestment

09/2018 - 12/2018

iOS junior

Grand

06/2017 - 09/2018

iOS Junior

Techno Masr

06/2016 - 06/2017

EDUCATION

Pharmacy

Azhar University

Full-Stack Web Development

ALMakinah

03/2017 - 06/2017

Courses

+600 hours Front-end and Back-end Bootcamp

iOS Development

Udemy

Courses

- iOS 11 App Development Bootcamp/ Angela yu
- Udemy iOS 11 and Swift 4 From Beginner to Paid Professional / Mark price
- Ray Wenderelich Course

SKILLS

Ruby & Ruby on Rails Framwork

JavaScript & jQuery library

ReactJS

CSS / Bootstrap

Source Control /Github- bitbucket

swift

Autolayouts

Core Data / Realm

Design Patterns / MVC, MVVM

Animation

iOS SDKs

Firebase

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Nagliat App (12/2017 – 02/2018) 🗹

Wuzfone 🗹

- app for jobs
- there are two users job seeker and activist

New Avenue 🗹

app for real estate companies

Doja Agent 🗹

app for real estate companies

BenchMark Agent 🗹

app for real estate companie

ככה 🖪

Events and conferences Organization app.

SaloniDepot 🗹

DealatCity 🗹

EVERYDAY VALUABLE DISCOUNT OFFERS AND BEST SAVING DEALS

🗹 أتىلە - Atelier

LANGUAGES

INTERESTS

Reading

German

Movies